1. openBrowser(URL)
5. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
9. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
13. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
17. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
21. click(findTestObject("Login/btn-sign in"))
25. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
29. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/verify-succes-acount-login"))
33. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
37. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"))
41. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord("IPHONE 11 PRO 128 GB DEEP PURPLE", ENTER))
45. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-11-pro"))
49. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product"))
53. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
57. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
61. takeScreenshot()
65. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-trash"))
69. takeScreenshot()
73. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-confrim-yes"))
77. takeScreenshot()
81. closeBrowser()